Fall hard.
The Fall Guy is a action, comedy, romance film directed by David Leitch.
Fresh off an almost career-ending accident, stuntman Colt Seavers has to track down a missing movie star,
solve a conspiracy and try to win back the love of his life while still doing his day job.
Colt Seavers, played by Ryan Gosling.
Jody Moreno, played by Emily Blunt.
Tom Ryder, played by Aaron Taylor-Johnson.
Gail Meyer, played by Hannah Waddingham.
Iggy Starr, played by Teresa Palmer.
Alma Milan, played by Stephanie Hsu.
The Fall Guy is a 2024 American action comedy film directed by David Leitch and
written by Drew Pearce, loosely based on the 1980s TV series.
The plot follows a stuntman (Ryan Gosling) working on his ex-girlfriend's (Emily Blunt) directorial debut action film,
only to find himself involved in a conspiracy surrounding the film's lead actor (Aaron Taylor-Johnson).
The cast also features Hannah Waddingham, Teresa
Palmer, Stephanie Hsu, and Winston Duke.
The Fall Guy premiered at SXSW on March 12, 2024, and it was released
in the United States on May 3 by Universal Pictures.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics, yet it underperformed at the box office, grossing $181
million worldwide against a $125–150 million production budget and losing the studio around $50 million.
The film explores themes of movie business, stuntman,
missing person, duringcreditsstinger, thoughtful.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.